autogeek.net 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy

Effective Date: Jan 1, 2017

Autogeek (“Company”) respects your privacy, and takes the responsibility of protecting the personal and business information that you provide to us via the Autogeek.com website (the “Site”) very seriously. To that end, Company herein discloses its privacy practices and the possible uses of the information that it gathers via its Site (the “Privacy Policy”).

 **What information does Company collect?**

In order to purchase products via the Site, take part in promotional activities for Company’s products, obtain information from Company, or have questions answered by Company, Company may request and/or collect personal information that may include, without limitation, your first and last name, home address, shipping address, phone number, email address, credit or debit card number, and feedback on Company’s products (“Personal Information”). By entering Personal Information on the Site, you consent to our use of the Personal Information for purposes related to the Site and the products offered and/or provided on or in connection with the Site. Without limiting the foregoing, by giving us Personal Information you are giving us, as well as third parties engaged by us, permission to contact you and/or send you promotional and/or other marketing information about products and offerings. If you elect to receive such promotional and/or marketing information, you may opt-out of receiving such materials by following the opt-out instructions contained in the materials or by emailing Company at info@Autogeek.com. Company does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from or about a child under the age of 13 without the consent of the child’s parent or legal guardian. If we discover that we have inadvertently collected information from a child under 13 years of age, we will promptly take all reasonable measures to delete that data from our systems.

 **Information Sharing**

Company may disclose your Personal Information to its affiliates, as well as third party partners that: (a) assist Company in fulfilling orders from customers; and (b) provide promotional services on behalf of Company. Company may also disclose your Personal Information if required or permitted to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights or property of Company or the users of the Site, or to act under urgent circumstances to protect the safety of Company or its employees or a member of the public. Company may disclose and/or transfer your Personal Information to a buyer or transferee of all or a portion of its assets in conjunction with the sale or transfer of such assets. Company may participate in bulk email solicitations that you have not consented to receiving (i.e., “spam”). Company does not sell or disclose client lists or email address lists to unrelated third parties. Except as otherwise provided herein; Company does not share Personal Information with any third party advertisers. However, Company may share aggregated anonymous information with third party advertisers, but this aggregated anonymous information cannot be matched with you personally unless you voluntarily share your Personal Information with the third party advertisers.

 **Use of cookies**

Like many companies, Company uses cookies and log files on the Site. A cookie is a small string of text that a website can send to your browser that is intended to enhance your visit. Personal Information that is contained in cookies will be protected to the same degree as any other Personal Information that we collect about you. While you may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings, some or all of the features of the Site may not function properly. We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. These third parties are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our Service Providers. However, we respect your right to choose whether to be included in such services. If you would like to opt out of these services, please contact us.

 **How do we protect your information?**

Company uses industry-standard security measures, including use of sophisticated encryption and authentication tools, to protect certain Personal Information. When the Site asks users to enter sensitive Personal Information, that Personal Information is protected with encryption software such as Secure Sockets Layer – SSL. Unfortunately, no data transmitted over or accessible through the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while Company attempts to protect all Personal Information, Company cannot ensure or warrant that any Personal Information will be completely secure from misappropriation by hackers or from other nefarious or criminal activities, or in the event of a failure of computer hardware, software, or a telecommunications network.

 **Third party links**

The Site may contain windows or hyperlinks which provide access to other websites not affiliated with Company. Your use of an external website or any informational content found on an external websites is subject to and governed by the terms and guidelines of said external website. Company does not endorse or make any representations or warranties concerning, and will not in any way be liable for, any informational content, products, services, software, or other materials available on an external website, even if one or more pages of the external website are framed within a page of this Site. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of any external website. For your protection, please refer to the terms of service and privacy policies of the respective external websites. Effective Date/Changes to our Privacy Policy This policy was last modified on April 26, 2018. Please note that Company may update this Privacy Policy from time-to-time, and you should check this page periodically for changes. If changes are made, Company will notify all users by stating the date the Privacy Policy was lasted modified.

 **Updating Information**

If you ever wish to access your Personal Information, or to have your Personal Information deleted, updated, changed or modified, you may do so by contacting Company by email at info@Autogeek.com

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below.

Vision Investments LLC Dba Autogeek,  
https://Autogeek.com/   
7744 SW Jack James Dr, Florida 34997  
info@Autogeek.com   
800-869-3011
